<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-rsses on Bitfolio</title>
    <link>https://timefrancesco.github.io/bitfolio/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-rsses on Bitfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://timefrancesco.github.io/bitfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://timefrancesco.github.io/bitfolio/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timefrancesco.github.io/bitfolio/post/first/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-can-t-choose-the-currency-when-adding-a-transaction&#34;&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t choose the currency when adding a transaction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transactions use the default currency, you can set it in settings, tap the cob icon in the Portfolio screen and choose you default currency.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-is-the-portfolio-chart-and-value-calculated&#34;&gt;How is the portfolio chart and value calculated?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the value of your assets at any given time.&lt;br /&gt;
If you own 1 bitcoin, it will show the value of it over a specified period of time, starting from the day before the date specified when entering the transaction.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-portfolio-chart-doesn-t-match-the-value-above&#34;&gt;The portfolio chart doesn&amp;rsquo;t match the value above&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There could be some small differences between the graph and the numeric value above it.
This is because the total value is calculated every minute with the latest currency valuation, while the chart uses the closing price up to the previous day.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-does-sale-and-sell-transactions-impact-calculations&#34;&gt;How does sale and sell transactions impact calculations?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When adding a sale/sell transaction, the percentage gain calculate would be based on the total average price paid for the coin.
Example: Bought 1 BTC for 100 (I wish&amp;hellip;), sold 0.50 when value of 1 BTC was 200 with a sale price of 100, total price paid calculate will be 50.
This will not be the correct total price paid but based on the average paid for the amount of crypto bought.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-i-cannot-delete-a-buy-transaction-it-says-something-about-being-linked&#34;&gt;Why I cannot delete a buy transaction, it says something about being linked?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you added an exchange transaction, it is not possible to remove the buy transaction from which the coins where then subsequentially exchanged.
You have to first remove the exchange transaction and then you will be able to remove the buy transaction.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-total-percentage-in-portfolio-view-doesn-t-add-up-to-the-single-coin-percentage-in-detail-view&#34;&gt;The total percentage in portfolio view doesn&amp;rsquo;t add up to the single coin percentage in detail view&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exchange and sell transactions can impact calculations of percentage.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-i-need-to-add-the-coin-price-when-adding-an-exchange-transaction&#34;&gt;Why I need to add the coin price when adding an exchange transaction?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When entering an exchange transaction, the price of a single coin is required to calculate the total value of your portfolio and your percentage gains.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-many-ticker-and-transactions-can-i-add&#34;&gt;How many ticker and transactions can I add?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Int64: more than you can imagine.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-s-icloud-sync&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s iCloud Sync?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If enabled, it synchronize your tickers and transactions among your iOS devices.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;is-it-safe-can-others-see-my-transaction&#34;&gt;Is it safe? Can others see my transaction?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s very safe and nobody except you can see your transactions in iCloud.&lt;br /&gt;
Safety and privacy are guaranteed by Apple, nobody not even the developers can access your private database, ever.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-question-is-not-here&#34;&gt;My question is not here&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head to the settings inside Bitfolio and tap the &amp;ldquo;Feedback&amp;rdquo; button, you will be able to send us an email.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>